One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
That's why we gotta cast off - together, we can!
Sailing from sea to sea,
saying it's nothing but a fairy tale.
Truth is stranger than fiction, isn't it?
Don't pretend you can't see it.
Common sense is only what the majority says it is!
It's not like we've seen
the end of the world with our own eyes.
So let's go, Captain I'll-Do-It-My-Way!
Whaddya mean, "no can do"?
We haven't even started yet!
I wanna know it all! Now, yes, we can!
Yes, we can! You can! This moment...
We can! I can! With this feeling of freedom...
Now... Now, oh yes, we can!
Yes, we can!
The Curly Hat Pirates Arrive
1,000,000 BELLY
It must be the ancient version of the Elephant Fruit. You ate such a rare fruit!
They've still got this many soldiers.
You should've withdrawn while the dog was treating you nicely!
Master!
We have just as many soldiers as some major countries!
Bepo!
You-gara guys are still under my care!
You don't need to fight!
It's not gonna work that way, Master!
Although I became a pirate, this is still my home!
To us...
It's our friend's home!
Don't speak as if you're full-fledged.
I'll destroy everything!
We'll fight back!
It's already morning!
Haven't you given up yet, Jack?!
We rotated our combatants by day and night...
and continued fighting for two days, three days, four days, and so on.
But Jack's reinforcements kept coming from the sea and we could hardly fend them off.
It was like fighting a wave of countless zombies!
However we were steadily overwhelming the enemy!
I can say there was only one that we couldn't bring down and that was...
...Jack!
He is, indeed, a monster!
Hmmm.
The guy who even this old man couldn't beat was Kaido's subordinate.
Unbelievable!
But the enemy was having a hard time too.
I think Jack got tired of the two rulers who he couldn't take down
so he finally brought out a weapon on the fifth day!
It was...
...a poison-gas weapon.
It all happened so quickly.
The deadly gas was filling the whole country at the speed of a blast wave!
How could anyone escape that?!
The gas filled up the whole city and half of the forest and totally paralyzed us.
Except for the people who evacuated to the back of the fortress, nearly everyone was incapacitated.
I don't even want to remember...
...what happened after that!
Answer the question!
Where's the warrior from the Land of Wano?
He's not here!
They kept asking questions they knew the answer to!
Then they brutalized our soldiers and ruined our country!
Then, they found Master Nekomamushi and the Guardians who were paralyzed by the gas...
...and did the same to them.
But when they saw they weren't getting anywhere...
Our tough ones were crucified...
...and tortured.
Where's the warrior from the Land of Wano?!
I don't know!
We wouldn't hide anyone like that!
Please stop...
No one in this country knows anything about that!
We're really dying for nothing! You have no mercy!
I won't let this go even if I die, Jack!
Until the day I curse you-gara to death with my cat-grudge!
Those tragic events lasted one whole day... and on the sixth day...
maybe because Jack was satisfied with the destruction or tired of hearing the same answer...
he left a few dozen of his men behind and departed from the island.
That's too awful!
There was no salvation.
No, that actually saved us too.
Oh, you were up!
I noticed that when I read Jack's obituary in the newspaper.
The prominent member of the Beasts Pirates
"Jack the Drought"
Jack dies!
Oh, so this is Jack.
The day you-gara people took down Doflamingo,
Jack left this country.
He left here to go save Doflamingo.
I guess they had some sort of a deep connection.
So the ones who drove that monster out of here were...
...you-gara people.
He fell asleep again!
I see!
Given all that, I'm even more grateful to you all and feel it was truly a miracle!
We arrived here the very next day after Jack left!
Is that...
...Zou?!
I warn you!
I don't like the idea of landing here!
You bastards!
Shut up and keep going!
Damn! I'll get even with you buttholes!
Is that...
Sanji-kun!
The gate is...
Seems like it was broken open with tremendous force.
There was obviously an invasion!
A-An invasion?!
Are they our enemies too?!
Brook! Look after Nami-san here. I'll go check inside.
No problem.
I-I'll look after Onami too!
Chopper! Caesar! Let's go!
Why should I go along...
Shut up and get moving!
See you later!
Don't take too long!
It looks abandoned.
There's no guard or gatekeeper. What happened?
Somebody, help!
Wh-What is it?!
What?!
Was she the one who talked?!
What's going on?!
Oh, he definitely looks like a villain!
That means she is a victim!
This way!
Wait, you little squirrel!
We just wanna crucify you and ask some questions!
Who are you guys?!
Brook! Can you handle them?!
Okay.
Go!
Soul Parade!
Ice Burn!
Yes!
Good job, Bonekichi!
Thank you, Brook!
A talking skeleton and eel!
I'm scared!
Wait! Hey, you!
What's happening on this island?!
What's going on here?!
It's filled with gas.
Are those all animals on the ground?!
Idiot! They're the Mink Tribe!
Don't you know?!
Anyway, let's go back to the forest for now!
We'll be killed by the gas!
Hey, you-gara people...
Tsk! Seems like they're still alive.
You're not their-gara's allies, are you?
I'm Pedro! Will you help me?
Please!
Duke Inuarashi and Master Nekomamushi need to be treated as soon as possible!
Otherwise, they're going to die...
The world is waiting for them.
Those two men...
We shall never ever...
...let them die!
Zou, 10 days ago
Boy! I can't believe it!
The whole country has been ravaged by the poison gas!
I got the chills seeing its power!
What's so funny?!
The name of the gas is Koro!
It's a weapon of mass destruction that I invented!
What did you just say?
I said that gas was made by me...
What?! Why should I take the blame?!
I'm not the one who used it!
This guy is the worst!
If you hadn't made it, no one would've fallen victim to it!
I'm sure you can neutralize it with your ability!
Do it now!
Then, make an antidote!
It's not too late yet!
Considering how much it cleared away, more than a day has passed already!
Not again!
Hey! Don't think the underdogs are always good!
The Mink Tribe is known for disliking humans and their great fighting strength!
Leave them alone for your own good!
They'll bite us to death as soon as we save them!
Bite us to death?
I'm losing my power...
It's salty! It's seawater!
Chopper!
Couldn't you save me a little more gently?!
Stop complaining after I saved you!
That's Nami-san's voice!
Listen, Caesar!
Get the poison gas you created out of the city before I come back!
What?!
Otherwise, I'll crush your heart here in my fist and...
Alright! You devil!
Sanji, leave him in my hands.
Yeah, thanks!
There she is!
Brook!
Keep stalling him like that!
Huh?!
Diable! Mouton...
Devil Mutton
Shot!
Sheepshead-sama!
Guys! Retreat!
Sheepshead-sama has been taken down!
What?!
But we haven't found the samurai yet!
Although we cornered them this far, he didn't show himself!
The samurai's not here! Tell him so!
Yes, ma'am!
Do it! Neutralize the gas!
How annoying. All right. I'll do it! Are you happy now?!
Koro-neutralizing gas!
This is so against my will!
Roko!
Okay, it's good!
Hey! Guys!
Get over here now!
That's Chopperemon!
From the forest down below!
Let's go now! There's no time to lose!
Th-This is awful!
Were they all killed by Caesar's weapon?!
Yeah. Most of the people have been wiped out.
It must've been done by those fools from earlier.
You mean those people who just attacked us?
Seems like Caesar neutralized the gas successfully...
But they've done so much damage.
So there is a chance that a lot of them are still hiding somewhere on the island.
According to the gas idiot, the Mink Tribe is a savage race.
We might end up regretting that we saved them but...
Are you-teia guys Jack's allies too?!
Nami-san!
Wait! It's okay!
She's weakened by the poison!
Nami-san! She has an explosive!
What?!
I'll never forgive you-teia people! Never!
What did we do to you?!
What do you gain from killing us?!
The person you-teia are looking for isn't here!
This country has a millennium-long history!
How much do you have to destroy to get your fill?!
Wanda-san!
Those-teia people saved me!
Tristan!
All of Jack's subordinates have just
left the island!
What? Left?
Did they-teia?
Pedro!
Wanda...
They-gara have nothing to do with Jack.
The poison gas has just cleared away from the city...
...because of their-gara magic.
Come to think of it, the gas is gone.
You-teia people...
Who are you?
What are you guys doing?!
Chopper!
More than a day has passed since the gas was released!
To counteract this gas, we have to give the poisoned ones
the antidote within 48 hours or it'll be too late for them!
What's that?
What?
To save everybody in the country, we can't even waste a second!
Where is there a hospital?! I need more instruments and medicine!
Bring everybody who can help here!
I'm a doctor! Do as I say!
Are you going to... save us?
I thought we were going to die... All of us!
We won't give up on anybody!
I'll play some soothing music.
You didn't even know who we were!
But you saved us without giving up.
We'll never forget what you did for us!
We'll pay our debt to you someday!
No, no! You don't have to do that!
You guys did such a nice thing!
I'm so proud of you!
I can't believe it was that serious...
Now I understand why we were so welcomed.
Anyway, that Jack guy makes me mad!
I'll kick his butt as well as Kaido's someday!
But he said there was an obituary...
Well, it's hard to believe if you had seen him with your own eyes.
Guys, will you stay here and talk?
Are you gonna go somewhere, Chopper?
It's night now so I'll go examine Nekomamushi, the King of the Night, and the Guardians of the Whale Forest!
Oh, I'll take you there with my Warney.
Come to think of it, Wanda,
isn't it time for you to sleep too?
I work as a Kingsbird.
A Kingsbird?
Yes - an aide to the kings and the only office that is
allowed to go back and forth between them regardless of whether it's day or night.
Wow, that's an important job!
I have to tell him that Duke Inuarashi is okay.
He'd probably say it's unnecessary.
I'll come with you!
I wanna see Nekomamushi!
Master Nekomamushi! I like him so much! I'll come with you!
It's a full moon tonight but I'm glad that it's covered by the clouds.
Be careful!
Okay!
Thank you, Carrot, for giving us a ride.
That's okay. I'm a Kingsbird too.
Anyway, Wanda, so far in your story...
Yeah, both Twirly Eyebrows and Gassy hadn't left yet.
Let me tell you what happened to them.
The thing is we didn't tell that many people in this country about this.
We didn't want to make the people who had their country ruined worry more.
This was a big event that happened secretly just two days ago.
Please be prepared for what you're going to hear.
Sanji-san might not...
...come back to us.
What?!
Whoa-whoa.
Why, Brook?!
It says "I'll be back" in his note!
I told you it's actually more complicated!
He will be back! I believe in Sanji!
Okay, okay, please relax, Luffy-san.
I'll tell you what happened from the beginning.
Uh-huh!
This island of Zou that we're on is the Phantom Island.
Because the island itself is a living thing, you can't get here even with a Log Pose
or find it in a normal way.
But...
We made a blunder and had a blind spot.
First, at that time...
You go ahead and sail for Zou!
We allowed the enemy ship that we'd shaken off to know our destination.
Second, someone from the Phantom Island was on their ship.
So the ones who showed up in front of us two days ago were...
...Emperor Big Mom's pirate group!
Clank.
We arrived.
Yeah, no problem. Count on us, Mama.
The two of us can finish this.
Zou is where I came from! Grr!